<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
    <XenotypeDef>
        <defName>MBSXT_Damphir</defName>
        <label>damphir</label>
        <description>Dampirs got their name from ancient tales of offspring between vampires and humans. Their actual origin is not too far off, as they are the results of a scientist attempting to reduce the negative impacts Sanguophages abilities cause. While they do not have the near-immortality that Sanguophages have, they do still maintain some of the abilities while also having enough in common with baseliners to fit in.\n\nDamphir must regular consume hemogen derived from human blood, much like Sanguophages. Unlike their predecessors, they do not need to deathrest or consume blood as frequently, and do not have any notable weakness to sunlight or fire. In exchange, they lack many of their innate abilities, and some abilities are weaker.\n\nThe first Damphir was created by a descendant of the lord-explorer Varan-Dur, Dan-Valin. Unfortunately, Dan-Valin did not live long enough to live long enough to say whether his creation was a success, as he had been killed trying to escape his underground lab when it was stormed by the local military.</description>
        <descriptionShort>Dampirs got their name from ancient tales of offspring between vampires and humans. Their actual origin is not too far off, as they are the results of a scientist attempting to reduce the negative impacts Sanguophages abilities cause. While they do not have the near-immortality that Sanguophages have, they do still maintain some of the abilities while also having enough in common with baseliners to fit in.Damphir must regular consume hemogen derived from human blood, much like Sanguophages. Unlike their predecessors, they do not need to deathrest or consume blood as frequently, and do not have any notable weakness to sunlight or fire.</descriptionShort>
        <iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/Sanguophage</iconPath>
        <inheritable>true</inheritable>
        <combatPowerFactor>1.5</combatPowerFactor>
        <displayPriority>-900</displayPriority>
        <factionlessGenerationWeight>0</factionlessGenerationWeight>
        <doubleXenotypeChances>
            <Pigskin>0.02</Pigskin>
            <Impid>0.02</Impid>
            <Yttakin>0.02</Yttakin>
            <Neanderthal>0.02</Neanderthal>
            <Waster>0.02</Waster>
            <Dirtmole>0.02</Dirtmole>
        </doubleXenotypeChances>
        <genes>
            <li>Hemogenic</li>
            <li>Ageless</li>
            <li>Beauty_Pretty</li>
            <li>DarkVision</li>
            <li>WoundHealing_Fast</li>
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Social</li>
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Intellectual</li>
            <li>ArchiteMetabolism</li>
            <li>Aggression_Aggressive</li>
            <li>Robust</li>
            <li>Superclotting</li>
            <li MayRequire="LibidoGenes.Mod">Libido_VeryLow</li>
        </genes>
    </XenotypeDef>

    <XenotypeDef>
        <defName>MBSXT_Viperal</defName>
        <label>viperal</label>
        <description>Viperal are bioengineered assassins, intended to be able to infiltrate any place and kill any target. Their numbers only increase when an individual is transformed into a Viperal, and their genetic code was designed to ensure that their lifespan would not be long enough to cause long term issues for their creaters. While some have managed to extend their lifespan to be similar to other xenotypes, it is always through extensive body replacement and countless surgeries.\n\nThe first Viperal were created to deal with an uprising of Hussar. Dr. Cyra Helios, the lead genetic scientist of the overtaken outpost, had the idea to create them when their most recent attempts to create more destructive Hussar backfired. The resulting eight Viperals killed all 30 Hussar by first sacrificing one of their own to burn the Hussar food and go-juice supply. After that they then began picking off the rapidly weakening Hussar one by one.</description>
        <descriptionShort>Viperal are bioengineered assassins, intended to be able to infiltrate any place and kill any target. Their numbers only increase when an individual is transformed into a Viperal, and their genetic code was designed to ensure that their lifespan would not be long enough to cause long term issues for their creaters. While some have managed to extend their lifespan to be similar to other xenotypes, it is always through extensive body replacement and countless surgeries.</descriptionShort>
        <iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/Hussar</iconPath>
        <combatPowerFactor>1.5</combatPowerFactor>
        <genes>
            <li>PsychicAbility_Deaf</li>
            <li>NakedSpeed</li>
            <li>Aggression_DeadCalm</li>
            <li>MeleeDamage_Strong</li>
            <li>KillThirst</li>
            <li>Sterile</li>
            <li>DarkVision</li>
            <li>Instability_Major</li>
            <li>Unstoppable</li>
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Shooting</li>
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Melee</li>
            <li>AptitudePoor_Construction</li>
            <li>AptitudePoor_Cooking</li>
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Plants</li>
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Animals</li>
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Crafting</li>
            <li>AptitudePoor_Artistic</li>
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Medicine</li>
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Social</li>
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Intellectual</li>
            <li MayRequire="LibidoGenes.Mod">Libido_ExtremelyLow</li>
        </genes>
    </XenotypeDef>

    <XenotypeDef>
        <defName>MBSXT_Artifexian</defName>
        <label>artifexian</label>
        <description>Artifexians enjoy making things, and their evolution has lended an extra hand to this endeavor. As much as they love building things, their evolution has also aided some of their lazier tendencies, specifically those that involve sleeping more and ignoring inconvenient things. They usually don't try to start fights with others, but theyare never willing to let an insult go unanswered. Should they find themselves in real danger, they may choose to call the local animals to fight on their behalf.\n\nArtifexians are evolved monkeys from a jungle planet that was found a few hundred years ago. While the ones who made initial contact with them always felt extreme caution about what they said to the Artifexians, they were willing to acknowledge that Artifexians great potential for helping claim new lands and building new cities.</description>
        <descriptionShort>Artifexians enjoy making things, and their evolution has lended an extra hand to this endeavor. As much as they love building things, their evolution has also aided some of their lazier tendencies, specifically those that involve sleeping more and ignoring inconvenient things. They usually don't try to start fights with others, but theyare never willing to let an insult go unanswered. Should they find themselves in real danger, they may choose to call the local animals to fight on their behalf.</descriptionShort>
        <iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/Yttakin</iconPath>
        <inheritable>true</inheritable>
        <combatPowerFactor>1.2</combatPowerFactor>
        <genes>
            <li>AnimalWarcall</li>
            <li>PsychicAbility_Deaf</li> 
            <li>MoveSpeed_Slow</li> 
            <li>NakedSpeed</li>
            <li>MinTemp_SmallIncrease</li> 
            <li>MaxTemp_SmallIncrease</li>
            <li>Aggression_Aggressive</li> 
            <li>KindInstinct</li> 
            <li>VerySleepy</li>
            <li>Robust</li> 
            <li>Pain_Reduced</li> 
            <li>StrongStomach</li> 
            <li>RobustDigestion</li> 
            <li>Nearsighted</li> 
            <li>ElongatedFingers</li>
            <li>Furskin</li>
            <li>Tail_Smooth</li> 
            <li>VoiceRoar</li> 
            <li>AptitudeTerrible_Shooting</li> 
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Construction</li>
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Crafting</li> 
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Artistic</li>
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Social</li>
            <li>Body_Standard</li> 
            <li>Body_Thin</li> 
            <li MayRequire="LibidoGenes.Mod">Libido_AboveAverage</li>
        </genes>
    </XenotypeDef>

    <XenotypeDef>
        <defName>MBSXT_Felionkin</defName>
        <label>felionkin</label>
        <description>Felionkin are human-cat hybrids that are remarkably lazy, often avoiding work that involves moving around or urgency. While they are often calm and very affectionate with their chosen individual, they have a hunting instinct that drives them to hunt other living things any time they grow too bored.\n\nFelionkin came into being not long after Pigskin were made. Once scientists realized that hybrids would frequently end up with human-like appearances, Dr. Maximus Quantum decided to try create two new types of genetic soldiers, preferably ones more controllable than the Hussar. The results were the Felionkin, instinctive hunters, and the Canuskin, loyal guardians.</description>
        <descriptionShort>Felionkin are human-cat hybrids that are remarkably lazy, often avoiding work that involves moving around or urgency. While they are often calm and very affectionate with their chosen individual, they have a hunting instinct that drives them to hunt other living things if they grow too bored.</descriptionShort>
        <iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/Baseliner</iconPath>
        <inheritable>true</inheritable>
        <combatPowerFactor>1.5</combatPowerFactor>
        <genes>
            <li>PsychicBonding</li> 
            <li>MoveSpeed_VeryQuick</li> 
            <li>NakedSpeed</li>
            <li>Mood_Sanguine</li>
            <li>MinTemp_SmallDecrease</li> 
            <li>MaxTemp_SmallIncrease</li>
            <li>FireTerror</li> 
            <li>Aggression_DeadCalm</li> 
            <li>MeleeDamage_Strong</li>
            <li>KillThirst</li> 
            <li>KindInstinct</li> 
            <li>VerySleepy</li> 
            <li>Delicate</li> 
            <li>Pain_Extra</li> 
            <li>Beauty_Beautiful</li> 
            <li>Ears_Cat</li>
            <li>StrongStomach</li> 
            <li>RobustDigestion</li> 
            <li>Nearsighted</li>
            <li>DarkVision</li>
            <li>Tail_Furry</li> 
            <li>AptitudeTerrible_Shooting</li> 
            <li>AptitudeRemarkable_Melee</li>
            <li>AptitudePoor_Construction</li>
            <li>AptitudePoor_Mining</li>
            <li>AptitudePoor_Cooking</li>
            <li>AptitudePoor_Plants</li>
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Animals</li> 
            <li>AptitudePoor_Crafting</li>
            <li>AptitudePoor_Artistic</li>
            <li>AptitudePoor_Medicine</li>
            <li>AptitudeRemarkable_Social</li>
            <li>AptitudeRemarkable_Intellectual</li>
            <li>Body_Thin</li> 
            <li>Libido_High</li>
            <li>Fertile</li>
        </genes>
    </XenotypeDef>

    <XenotypeDef>
        <defName>MBSXT_Canuskin</defName>
        <label>canuskin</label>
        <description>Canuskin are human-dog hybrids that were bred to fight alongside their owners. They enjoy digging holes and herding animals, but tend to lack the skills required to do more mentally intensive tasks. They frequently start fights with other colonists to asert dominance. Unfortunately, they tend to live shorter lives than most xenotypes, largely due to genetic instability.\n\nCanuskin came into being not long after Pigskin were made. Once scientists realized that hybrids would frequently end up with human-like appearances, Dr. Maximus Quantum decided to try create two new types of genetic soldiers, preferably ones more controllable than the Hussar. The results were the Felionkin, instinctive hunters, and the Canuskin, loyal guardians.</description>
        <descriptionShort>Canuskin are human-dog hybrids that were bred to fight alongside their owners. They enjoy digging holes and herding animals, and they frequently start fights with other colonists to asert dominance.</descriptionShort>
        <iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/Baseliner</iconPath>
        <inheritable>true</inheritable>
        <combatPowerFactor>1.5</combatPowerFactor>
        <genes>
            <li>PsychicAbility_Deaf</li>
            <li>PsychicBonding</li> 
            <li>MoveSpeed_VeryQuick</li> 
            <li>NakedSpeed</li>
            <li>Mood_Sanguine</li>
            <li>MaxTemp_SmallDecrease</li>
            <li>FireTerror</li> 
            <li>Aggression_HyperAggressive</li> 
            <li>MeleeDamage_Strong</li>
            <li>KillThirst</li> 
            <li>KindInstinct</li> 
            <li>Sleepy</li> 
            <li>Robust</li> 
            <li>Pain_Reduced</li> 
            <li>Libido_High</li>
            <li>Fertile</li>
            <li>Beauty_Beautiful</li> 
            <li>Hair_LongOnly</li>
            <li>Ears_Floppy</li>
            <li>StrongStomach</li> 
            <li>RobustDigestion</li> 
            <li>Nearsighted</li>
            <li>DarkVision</li>
            <li>Instability_Mild</li>
            <li>Unstoppable</li>
            <li>Tail_Furry</li> 
            <li>AptitudeTerrible_Shooting</li> 
            <li>AptitudeRemarkable_Melee</li>
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Mining</li>
            <li>AptitudePoor_Cooking</li>
            <li>AptitudePoor_Plants</li>
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Animals</li> 
            <li>AptitudePoor_Crafting</li>
            <li>AptitudePoor_Artistic</li>
            <li>AptitudePoor_Medicine</li>
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Social</li>
            <li>AptitudePoor_Intellectual</li>
        </genes>
    </XenotypeDef>

    <XenotypeDef>
        <defName>MBSXT_Toxinborn</defName>
        <label>toxinborn</label>
        <description>Toxinborn are the less-violent cousins of Wasters. While they do still have a lot of the same resistances as Wasters, they lack the immunities and depency to pyscoid based drugs. This has led to their bodies becoming weaker overall, as their metabolisms becoming slowed down considerably. They avoid direct conflict at all costs, prefering to leave it to automated defenses and any violence inclined allies in the colony.\n\nThe differences between Wasters and Toxinborn largely appeared due to some Waster societies choosing to settle in one area, and focus on farming rather than the high of drugs and war. This does not mean they become helpless in post-apocalyptic deathworlds, as they often create massive settlements with automated turrets that let the Toxinborn farm in peace.</description>
        <descriptionShort>Toxinborn are the less-violent cousins of Wasters. While they do still have a lot of the same resistances as Wasters, they lack the immunities and depency to pyscoid based drugs. This has led to their bodies becoming weaker overall, as their metabolisms becoming slowed down considerably. They avoid direct conflict at all costs, prefering to leave it to automated defenses and any violence inclined allies in the colony.</descriptionShort>
        <iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/Waster</iconPath>
        <inheritable>true</inheritable>
        <combatPowerFactor>0.5</combatPowerFactor>
        <nameMaker>NamerPersonWaster</nameMaker>
        <genes>
            <li>Immunity_SuperStrong</li>
            <li>WoundHealing_Slow</li> 
            <li>PsychicAbility_Deaf</li> 
            <li>ToxResist_Total</li>
            <li>Aggression_DeadCalm</li>
            <li>Delicate</li> 
            <li>Pain_Extra</li>
            <li>Head_Gaunt</li> 
            <li>Hair_Gray</li> 
            <li>Skin_SlateGray</li> 
            <li>Instability_Mild</li> 
            <li>PollutionRush</li>
            <li>AptitudeTerrible_Shooting</li>
            <li>AptitudeTerrible_Melee</li> 
            <li>AptitudeRemarkable_Plants</li> 
        </genes>
    </XenotypeDef>

    <XenotypeDef>
        <defName>MBSXT_Reaver</defName>
        <label>reaver</label>
        <description>Reavers are psychic warriors who try to take all psychic artifacts that they can get their hands on. They have a high attunement to psionics, and their bodies are more suited for combat than anything else, usually at the expense of their mental acuity and longevity.\n\nUsually there is only one or two of Reavers in any group that truly has psychic abilities, but prolonged exposure to their powers and experiments over many generations has forcefully twisted Reaver's genetics to make them more prone to violent tendencies, and it has given them a durable body to better survive the results of those tendencies, usually at the expense of their mental acuity and longevity.</description>
        <descriptionShort>Reavers are psychic warriors who try to take all psychic artifacts that they can get their hands on. They have a high attunement to psionics, and their bodies are more suited for combat than anything else.</descriptionShort>
        <iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/Baseliner</iconPath>
        <inheritable>true</inheritable>
        <combatPowerFactor>2.0</combatPowerFactor>
        <genes>
            <li>Immunity_Weak</li>
            <li>WoundHealing_SuperFast</li> 
            <li>Superclotting</li> 
            <li>PsychicAbility_Extreme</li>
            <li>PsychicBonding</li> 
            <li>MoveSpeed_VeryQuick</li>
            <li>NakedSpeed</li> 
            <li>Mood_Depressive</li> 
            <li>FireResistant</li>
            <li>Aggression_HyperAggressive</li> 
            <li>MeleeDamage_Strong</li> 
            <li>KillThirst</li> 
            <li>Robust</li> 
            <li>Pain_Reduced</li> 
            <li>Libido_High</li>
            <li>Eyes_Red</li>
            <li>Body_Hulk</li> 
            <li>Hair_BrightRed</li> 
            <li>Skin_InkBlack</li> 
            <li>StrongStomach</li>
            <li>RobustDigestion</li> 
            <li>Learning_Slow</li>
            <li>DarkVision</li> 
            <li>Instability_Major</li> 
            <li>Unstoppable</li>
            <li>AptitudeRemarkable_Shooting</li> 
            <li>AptitudeRemarkable_Melee</li> 
            <li>AptitudePoor_Construction</li> 
            <li>AptitudePoor_Mining</li> 
            <li>AptitudePoor_Cooking</li> 
            <li>AptitudePoor_Plants</li> 
            <li>AptitudePoor_Animals</li> 
            <li>AptitudePoor_Crafting</li> 
            <li>AptitudePoor_Artistic</li> 
            <li>AptitudePoor_Medicine</li> 
            <li>AptitudeTerrible_Social</li> 
            <li>AptitudeTerrible_Intellectual</li> 
            <li MayRequire="FertilityGenes.Mod">VeryLowFertility</li>
        </genes>
    </XenotypeDef>

    <XenotypeDef>
        <defName>MBSXT_Harmonite</defName>
        <label>harmonite</label>
        <description>Harmonites are archite enhanced psychics who are usually calming influences within societies. Their dependency on the archites in their bloodstream and their superior psycic abilities has weakened their bodies over many generations, though their minds have been enhanced by the very forces that weakened their bodies. The archites in their blood have rendered them nigh-immortal, even as their frail bodies fail to heal the most minor of wounds at a normal rate.\n\nXenia Nebula was the first harmonite to be created after an interaction with an archite gene-scrambler. All harmonites descended from her, many of them looking similar to the general appearance of those within the society they live in.</description>
        <descriptionShort>Harmonites are archite enhanced psychics who are usually calming influences within societies. Their dependency on the archites in their bloodstream and their superior psycic abilities has weakened their bodies over many generations, though their minds have been enhanced by the very forces that weakened their bodies. The archites in their blood have rendered them nigh-immortal, even as their frail bodies fail to heal the most minor of wounds at a normal rate.</descriptionShort>
        <iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/Baseliner</iconPath>
        <inheritable>true</inheritable>
        <combatPowerFactor>0.8</combatPowerFactor>
        <genes>
            <li>Ageless</li>
            <li>ArchiteMetabolism</li> 
            <li>Deathless</li> 
            <li>DiseaseFree</li>
            <li>PerfectImmunity</li> 
            <li>TotalHealing</li>
            <li>WoundHealing_Slow</li> 
            <li>PsychicAbility_Extreme</li> 
            <li>PsychicBonding</li>
            <li>NakedSpeed</li> 
            <li>Mood_Sanguine</li> 
            <li>MinTemp_SmallIncrease</li> 
            <li>MaxTemp_SmallDecrease</li> 
            <li>Aggression_DeadCalm</li> 
            <li>MeleeDamage_Weak</li>
            <li>KindInstinct</li>
            <li>Sleepy</li> 
            <li>Beauty_Beautiful</li> 
            <li>Body_Thin</li> 
            <li>Learning_Fast</li>
            <li>Nearsighted</li> 
            <li>DarkVision</li> 
            <li>Instability_Major</li> 
            <li>AptitudeTerrible_Shooting</li> 
            <li>AptitudeTerrible_Melee</li> 
            <li>AptitudePoor_Construction</li> 
            <li>AptitudePoor_Mining</li> 
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Cooking</li> 
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Crafting</li> 
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Artistic</li> 
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Medicine</li> 
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Social</li> 
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Intellectual</li> 
            <li MayRequire="LibidoGenes.Mod">Libido_ExtremelyLow</li>
            <li MayRequire="FertilityGenes.Mod">ExtremelyLowFertility</li>
        </genes>
    </XenotypeDef>

    <XenotypeDef>
        <defName>MBSXT_Battleborne</defName>
        <label>battleborne</label>
        <description>The Battleborne are natural leaders, both during times of war and times of peace. They never need to rest, and their genetics renders them immune to the effects of various psychic effects. While their bodies are naturally suited for both intellectual work and melee combat, they are also reliant on various drugs to continue functioning.\n\nBattleborne was what Dr. Cyra Helios decided to create after seeing the effectiveness of the Viperal. The idea behind the Battleborne was to have a xenotype that could fit in with, and to an extent control, Hussar groups while also being more controllable. The resulting go-juice, pschite, and wake-up depencies were intentional, as they enhanced the Battleborne's ability, in addition to providing an easy way to keep them in line.</description>
        <descriptionShort>The Battleborne are natural leaders, both during times of war and times of peace. They never need to rest, and their genetics renders them immune to the effects of various psychic effects. While their bodies are naturally suited for both intellectual work and melee combat, they are also reliant on various drugs to continue functioning.</descriptionShort>
        <iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/Neanderthal</iconPath>
        <inheritable>true</inheritable>
        <combatPowerFactor>2.2</combatPowerFactor>
        <genes>
            <li>WoundHealing_SuperFast</li>
            <li>Superclotting</li> 
            <li>PsychicAbility_Deaf</li> 
            <li>Aggression_HyperAggressive</li>
            <li>MeleeDamage_Strong</li> 
            <li>KillThirst</li>
            <li>KindInstinct</li> 
            <li>Neversleep</li> 
            <li>Robust</li>
            <li>Pain_Reduced</li> 
            <li>Beauty_Beautiful</li> 
            <li>Eyes_Gray</li> 
            <li>Ears_Pointed</li> 
            <li>Jaw_Heavy</li> 
            <li>Body_Hulk</li>
            <li>Hair_SnowWhite</li>
            <li>Learning_Fast</li> 
            <li>Nearsighted</li> 
            <li>DarkVision</li> 
            <li>Instability_Major</li>
            <li>ElongatedFingers</li> 
            <li>Unstoppable</li>
            <li>Tail_Smooth</li> 
            <li>AptitudeTerrible_Shooting</li> 
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Melee</li>
            <li>AptitudePoor_Construction</li> 
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Crafting</li> 
            <li>AptitudePoor_Artistic</li> 
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Medicine</li> 
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Social</li> 
            <li>AptitudeStrong_Intellectual</li> 
            <li>ChemicalDependency_GoJuice</li> 
            <li>ChemicalDependency_Psychite</li> 
            <li>ChemicalDependency_WakeUp</li> 
        </genes>
    </XenotypeDef>

    <XenotypeDef>
        <defName>MBSXT_Oni</defName>
        <label>oni</label>
        <description>Oni evolved on a harsh post-apocalyptic desert deathworld. They first got their name due to their red appearances and horns, and the name stuck when they demonstrated their violent tendencies. Usually the only times they are happy are the times when they can obey their innate desire for destruction, or their desire to do nothing but eat and sleep.\n\nOccassionally, outlander outposts will be abandoned if a large group of Oni are gathering nearby. Most outlanders believe that when multiple Oni are in the same area, they will start a fight that results in every settlment in the area being destroyed.</description>
        <descriptionShort>Oni evolved on a harsh post-apocalyptic desert deathworld. They first got their name due to their red appearances and horns, and the name stuck when they demonstrated their violent tendencies. Usually the only times they are happy are the times when they can obey their innate desire for destruction, or their desire to do nothing but eat and sleep.</descriptionShort>
        <iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/Impid</iconPath>
        <inheritable>true</inheritable>
        <combatPowerFactor>1.8</combatPowerFactor>
        <nameMaker>NamerPersonImpid</nameMaker>
        <chanceToUseNameMaker>1</chanceToUseNameMaker>
        <genes>
            <li>FireSpew</li>
            <li>Immunity_SuperStrong</li>
            <li>WoundHealing_SuperFast</li>
            <li>Superclotting</li> 
            <li>PsychicAbility_Deaf</li> 
            <li>Mood_Depressive</li>
            <li>MinTemp_SmallIncrease</li>
            <li>MaxTemp_LargeIncrease</li>
            <li>ToxResist_Total</li>
            <li>FireResistant</li>
            <li>Aggression_HyperAggressive</li>
            <li>MeleeDamage_Strong</li> 
            <li>KillThirst</li>
            <li>VerySleepy</li>
            <li>Robust</li>
            <li>Pain_Reduced</li> 
            <li>Beauty_VeryUgly</li> 
            <li>Eyes_Red</li> 
            <li>Headbone_MiniHorns</li> 
            <li>VoiceRoar</li>
            <li>Body_Hulk</li>
            <li>Hair_BrightRed</li>
            <li>Skin_DeepRed</li>
            <li>Learning_Slow</li> 
            <li>Nearsighted</li> 
            <li>Instability_Major</li>
            <li>ElongatedFingers</li> 
            <li>PollutionRush</li>
            <li>Unstoppable</li>
            <li>AptitudeTerrible_Shooting</li> 
            <li>AptitudeRemarkable_Melee</li>
            <li MayRequire="LibidoGenes.Mod">Libido_VeryHigh</li>
            <li MayRequire="FertilityGenes.Mod">LowFertility</li>
        </genes>
    </XenotypeDef>
</Defs>
